Norbertas Lapenas

Mobile: 085 114-9751 27 The Meadows, Email: nlapenas@gmail.com Oldgrange Wood, Website: https://norbertasl.github.io/ Monasterevin,

GitHub: https://github.com/NorbertasL Co.Kildare.

Personal Profile

An individual with a positive attitude and a natural understanding of logical thinking. Skilled at problem solving in a calm and organized manner. A team player with a self motivated mentality. Currently seeking the opportunity to start a career in "Software Development"

Education, Qualification & Training

2019 Full Stack Developer Course – On-line with Code Institute

2019 County Kildare Leader Partnership, Jigginstown, Naas, Co Kildare

Business Development Course

Marketing QQI Level 5

2016 Java SE 8 Associate Programmer Certificate

2010 Moyle Park College, Clondalkin, Dublin

Junior and Leaving Certificates completed. Best

student awards in 3rd and 5th year.

Key Skills Software Development & Achievement

Front End Skills Back End Skills:

HTML / HTML5	Java / Spring
CSS / CCS3 / Bootstrap	Python / Django
JavaScript / jQuery / AngularJS	SQL / noSQL
Responsive Design	REST API

General Skills:

Version Control /Git	Team Player
Problem Solver	 Self-Motivated/Self Driven
Maven framework	 Excellent communication skills

Career Summary

2010-2019 A Gilligan Builders, Ballymount Drive, Ballymount, Dublin 12

Role Construction Operative/Installer

Full time and part-time role since 2010. A high number of duties and responsibilities required a fast learning mentality and excellent communicative skills. Problem-solving skills were essential for this position.

2017-2018 Brendan McGee Construction, Monasterevin, Co Kildare

Role Construction Operative

Short-term role in a very fast pace building site environment. The role involved work-flow management and working as part of big teams.

2015-2017 Junction 14 Service Station, Monasterevin, Co Kildare

Role Delicatessen Assistant

Key roles and repositories involved serving customers in a very fast pace and busy environment. Great communication and interpersonal skills were a necessity. Excellent teamwork and time management skills were developed in this role.

2014-2015 Oxigen Environmental, Naas, Co Kildare

Role Environmental Refuse Collector

Part of a team of environmental refuse collectors providing a refuse collection service to customers throughout county Kildare.

Hobbies and Interests

- 3D Printing(I assembled my own in 2018).
- Electronics, I tinker with Arduino and Raspberry Pi.
- Motorbike and driving on the country roads.
- Mixed Martial Arts BJJ.
- Cycling Cycled from Netherlands to France just for the fun of it.
- A lot of reading I'm a real book-work, because books are the best way to learn something new.

References

References available on request.